<edimap xmlns:medi="http://www.milyn.org/schema/edi-message-mapping-1.5.xsd">
    <import namespace="UN" resource="__modelset_definitions.xml"/>
    <description name="IMPDEF" namespace="urn:org.milyn.edi.unedifact:un:d13a:impdef" version="D:13A:UN"/>
    <delimiters component=":" escape="?" field="+" segment="'!$" sub-component="~"/>
    <segments xmltag="IMPDEF">
        <segment ignoreUnmappedFields="false" maxOccurs="1" minOccurs="1" name="Beginning of message" nodeTypeRef="UN:BGM" segcode="BGM" truncatable="true" xmltag="BGM">
            <documentation>BGM,
        A segment to indicate the beginning of the message and to transmit
        function, type and number of the message.</documentation>
        </segment>
        <segment ignoreUnmappedFields="false" maxOccurs="1" minOccurs="1" name="Message type identification" nodeTypeRef="UN:MSG" segcode="MSG" truncatable="true" xmltag="MSG">
            <documentation>MSG,
        A segment identifying a message type to which the implementation
        details apply.</documentation>
        </segment>
        <segment ignoreUnmappedFields="false" maxOccurs="1" minOccurs="0" name="Requirements and conditions" nodeTypeRef="UN:RCS" segcode="RCS" truncatable="true" xmltag="RCS">
            <documentation>RCS,
        A segment specifying the distribution conditions for the
        implementation.</documentation>
        </segment>
        <segment ignoreUnmappedFields="false" maxOccurs="1" minOccurs="1" name="Directory identification" nodeTypeRef="UN:DII" segcode="DII" truncatable="true" xmltag="DII">
            <documentation>DII,
        A segment specifying the identity of the source directory set and
        giving its language and maintenance operation. This identifies the
        underlying standard from which the standard message is drawn.</documentation>
        </segment>
        <segment ignoreUnmappedFields="false" maxOccurs="99" minOccurs="0" name="Reference" nodeTypeRef="UN:RFF" segcode="RFF" truncatable="true" xmltag="RFF">
            <documentation>RFF,
        A segment carrying reference information for the implementation as
        a whole. This may specify the unique registration identifier of
        this implementation guide; it may carry references to graphical
        information to be used or displayed whenever the implementation is
        physically displayed.</documentation>
        </segment>
        <segment ignoreUnmappedFields="false" maxOccurs="9" minOccurs="0" name="Date/time/period" nodeTypeRef="UN:DTM" segcode="DTM" truncatable="true" xmltag="DTM">
            <documentation>DTM,
        A segment specifying dates related to the implementation guide,
        such as date of issue or date of approval.</documentation>
        </segment>
        <segment ignoreUnmappedFields="false" maxOccurs="999" minOccurs="0" name="Free text" nodeTypeRef="UN:FTX" segcode="FTX" truncatable="true" xmltag="FTX">
            <documentation>FTX,
        A segment providing implementation guide notes which relate to the
        implementation as a whole. It may also carry various legal or
        contractual phrases which may apply to the ownership or copyright
        of the implementation guide, or contractual terms which will be
        incorporated by reference into any contract of which a data
        transmission using this implementation is a part.</documentation>
        </segment>
        <segmentGroup maxOccurs="5" minOccurs="0" xmltag="Segment_group_1">
            <documentation>Segment group 1:
        A group of segments identifying the parties involved in the
        transaction with associated information. For publicly available
        implementation guides this includes details of the ownership and
        origination of the guide.</documentation>
            <segment ignoreUnmappedFields="false" maxOccurs="1" minOccurs="1" name="Party identification" nodeTypeRef="UN:PNA" segcode="PNA" truncatable="true" xmltag="PNA">
                <documentation>PNA,
           A segment identifying the names of the parties involved in the
           transaction, e.g., originator, requester, author or secretariat.</documentation>
            </segment>
            <segment ignoreUnmappedFields="false" maxOccurs="1" minOccurs="0" name="Address" nodeTypeRef="UN:ADR" segcode="ADR" truncatable="true" xmltag="ADR">
                <documentation>ADR,
           A segment identifying the address of the party.</documentation>
            </segment>
            <segmentGroup maxOccurs="9999" minOccurs="0" xmltag="Segment_group_2">
                <documentation>Segment group 2:
           A group of segments identifying a person or a department and
           identifying communication type and number.</documentation>
                <segment ignoreUnmappedFields="false" maxOccurs="1" minOccurs="1" name="Contact information" nodeTypeRef="UN:CTA" segcode="CTA" truncatable="true" xmltag="CTA">
                    <documentation>CTA,
              A segment identifying a person or a department for the party
              to whom the communication should be directed.</documentation>
                </segment>
                <segment ignoreUnmappedFields="false" maxOccurs="5" minOccurs="0" name="Communication contact" nodeTypeRef="UN:COM" segcode="COM" truncatable="true" xmltag="COM">
                    <documentation>COM,
              A segment identifying communication type and number of the
              person.</documentation>
                </segment>
            </segmentGroup>
        </segmentGroup>
        <segmentGroup maxOccurs="99999" minOccurs="0" xmltag="Segment_group_3">
            <documentation>Segment group 3:
        A group of segments to describe the usage of a segment, a segment
        group, a composite or an element, an alias, or a constraint in a
        MIG or IC. The iterations of this segment group form the bulk of
        the MIG or IC.
        
        The MIG or IC consists of a series of iterations of this segment
        group which describe the target message hierarchy. Within the
        hierarchy, additional occurrences of this segment group may specify
        the conditions or relationships between the components.
        
        Only the appropriate parts of this segment group should be used as
        necessary on any particular iteration. The other contained segment
        groups are ordered to minimise the number of iterations of this
        segment group. The 'Alias' and 'Constraint' instances of this
        segment group provide a mechanism for grouping or encapsulating
        blocks of components. An 'Alias' has no context, and therefore
        takes on the context of the point at which it is used. A
        'Constraint' inherits the context in which it is defined, but may
        redefine any part of its context by using the appropriate optional
        segment groups within the main segment loop. 
        
        As well as its defining function, each component may also be used
        in a constraining manner. For example, a repeating segment may not
        only define its components, but also the number of times it is
        allowed to repeat; then, within each instance, a different
        combination of element requirements may be expressed. This
        conditionality may be based on either ordering or content criteria.
        
        Once defined, an 'Alias' may be used throughout the MIG where
        required, by "using" the definition which is identified by its
        'name'. Similarly, in error reporting, an active constraint may be
        identified by its 'name'.</documentation>
            <segment ignoreUnmappedFields="false" maxOccurs="1" minOccurs="1" name="Definition function" nodeTypeRef="UN:DFN" segcode="DFN" truncatable="true" xmltag="DFN">
                <documentation>DFN,
           A segment identifying the object of the definition, and
           containing an optional 'name' or identifier.</documentation>
            </segment>
            <segment ignoreUnmappedFields="false" maxOccurs="99" minOccurs="0" name="Free text" nodeTypeRef="UN:FTX" segcode="FTX" truncatable="true" xmltag="FTX">
                <documentation>FTX,
           A segment providing implementation guide notes pertaining to the
           preceding definition, or to carry the text of a constraint
           expression.</documentation>
            </segment>
            <segmentGroup maxOccurs="1" minOccurs="0" xmltag="Segment_group_4">
                <documentation>Segment group 4:
           A group of segments identifying a segment group and providing
           details about segment group usage. This segment group depends on
           a segment context having been established by an instance of a
           segment group describing segment usage.
           
           This segment group defines a segment group context for the
           target message, and will immediately follow the definition of
           the trigger segment context, preceding the constituent elements
           within the trigger segment.
           
           Several instances of the same segment group may be described,
           with the MEA segment group distinguishing which range or
           instance of the target message segment is being described.</documentation>
                <segment ignoreUnmappedFields="false" maxOccurs="1" minOccurs="1" name="Segment group usage details" nodeTypeRef="UN:GRU" segcode="GRU" truncatable="true" xmltag="GRU">
                    <documentation>GRU,
              A segment specifying the usage of a segment group in a
              definition. The segment may identify one or more instances of
              a target segment group.</documentation>
                </segment>
                <segment ignoreUnmappedFields="false" maxOccurs="99" minOccurs="0" name="Free text" nodeTypeRef="UN:FTX" segcode="FTX" truncatable="true" xmltag="FTX">
                    <documentation>FTX,
              A segment providing implementation guide notes or textual
              information related to the specific group in the underlying
              message.</documentation>
                </segment>
            </segmentGroup>
            <segmentGroup maxOccurs="999" minOccurs="0" xmltag="Segment_group_5">
                <documentation>Segment group 5:
           A group of segments specifying segment usage within the
           definition. There will be at least one instance of this segment
           group for each segment described in the implementation guide.
           
           This segment group defines a segment context, and all the
           following components are deemed to be within the context of the
           segment whose usage is being defined until a subsequent segment
           context is defined.
           
           Several instances of the same segment may be described, with the
           MEA segment group distinguishing which range or instance of the
           target message segment is being described.</documentation>
                <segment ignoreUnmappedFields="false" maxOccurs="1" minOccurs="1" name="Segment usage details" nodeTypeRef="UN:SGU" segcode="SGU" truncatable="true" xmltag="SGU">
                    <documentation>SGU,
              A segment specifying the usage of a segment in a message type
              structure for this definition. As well as defining the
              specific usage of a particular target segment, this segment
              also provides the segment context for the following element
              usage details. The segment may identify one or more instances
              of usage for any particular segment in the target data
              message.</documentation>
                </segment>
                <segment ignoreUnmappedFields="false" maxOccurs="99" minOccurs="0" name="Free text" nodeTypeRef="UN:FTX" segcode="FTX" truncatable="true" xmltag="FTX">
                    <documentation>FTX,
              A segment providing implementation guide notes, or textual
              information relating to the specific segment in the
              underlying message.</documentation>
                </segment>
            </segmentGroup>
            <segmentGroup maxOccurs="99" minOccurs="0" xmltag="Segment_group_6">
                <documentation>Segment group 6:
           A group of segments specifying formalised relationships among
           the various components of this implementation at a particular
           context, such as additional rules concerning syntax and
           semantics which are specific to an implementation.
           
           The relationships may be both intra-component, such as between
           elements in a segment, or inter-component, such as between
           elements in different segments.
           
           Depending on the context in which this segment group is used, it
           may specify relationships between segments or segment groups in
           a message, between data elements in a segment, or between data
           elements in a composite.</documentation>
                <segment ignoreUnmappedFields="false" maxOccurs="1" minOccurs="1" name="Footnote" nodeTypeRef="UN:FNT" segcode="FNT" truncatable="true" xmltag="FNT">
                    <documentation>FNT,
              A segment specifying a footnote identification number that
              may place the relationship in the current context.</documentation>
                </segment>
                <segment ignoreUnmappedFields="false" maxOccurs="1" minOccurs="0" name="Relationship" nodeTypeRef="UN:REL" segcode="REL" truncatable="true" xmltag="REL">
                    <documentation>REL,
              A segment specifying a relationship between the various
              components, typically data elements in a segment, in the
              current context.</documentation>
                </segment>
                <segment ignoreUnmappedFields="false" maxOccurs="9" minOccurs="0" name="Related identification numbers" nodeTypeRef="UN:GIR" segcode="GIR" truncatable="true" xmltag="GIR">
                    <documentation>GIR,
              A segment identifying the various components in a
              relationship, typically data elements in a segment, in the
              current context.</documentation>
                </segment>
                <segment ignoreUnmappedFields="false" maxOccurs="99" minOccurs="0" name="Free text" nodeTypeRef="UN:FTX" segcode="FTX" truncatable="true" xmltag="FTX">
                    <documentation>FTX,
              A segment carrying text notes to the preceding relationship.</documentation>
                </segment>
            </segmentGroup>
            <segmentGroup maxOccurs="99" minOccurs="0" xmltag="Segment_group_7">
                <documentation>Segment group 7:
           A group of segments carrying references, or constraints whose
           default context applies to the containing segment. This segment
           group may be used to change the constraint mechanism at the
           current and deeper levels in the message hierarchy.
           Additionally, this segment group may be used to carry legal and
           contractual terms which relate, either by way of explanation or
           to be incorporated by reference, in the particular context at
           which the group appears.
           
           Depending on the context, the references may be applied to the
           target message as a whole, the current segment or element
           context, or the current code value context.</documentation>
                <segment ignoreUnmappedFields="false" maxOccurs="1" minOccurs="1" name="Reference" nodeTypeRef="UN:RFF" segcode="RFF" truncatable="true" xmltag="RFF">
                    <documentation>RFF,
              A segment identifying a reference document or a following
              constraint expression.</documentation>
                </segment>
                <segment ignoreUnmappedFields="false" maxOccurs="99" minOccurs="0" name="Free text" nodeTypeRef="UN:FTX" segcode="FTX" truncatable="true" xmltag="FTX">
                    <documentation>FTX,
              A segment carrying the text of a constraint expression or
              providing implementation guide notes pertaining to the
              preceding constraint.</documentation>
                </segment>
            </segmentGroup>
            <segmentGroup maxOccurs="99" minOccurs="0" xmltag="Segment_group_8">
                <documentation>Segment group 8:
           A group of segments specifying implementation requirements for
           data elements in the current segment or composite context.
           Multiple instances of this segment group will typically be used
           to describe the usage of all the elements in any given segment
           or composite context. There will be at least one instance of
           this segment group for each element used, although a constraint
           structure may override or further define the specification in
           any particular context or sub-context. The MEA segment group may
           be used to provide repeat range or specific instance information
           for repeating data elements.
           
           This segment group defines an element or composite context which
           will remain in force until the next element or composite context
           is defined, or a new segment context is established.</documentation>
                <segment ignoreUnmappedFields="false" maxOccurs="1" minOccurs="1" name="Data element usage details" nodeTypeRef="UN:ELU" segcode="ELU" truncatable="true" xmltag="ELU">
                    <documentation>ELU,
              A segment identifying the usage of a simple or composite data
              element in the current context. This segment starts a block
              of information about any one particular contextualised usage
              of a data element in a target data message.
              
              The data element usage determines whether this segment is
              defining a composite context, a simple element context or a
              component element context.</documentation>
                </segment>
                <segment ignoreUnmappedFields="false" maxOccurs="1" minOccurs="0" name="Simple data element details" nodeTypeRef="UN:ELM" segcode="ELM" truncatable="true" xmltag="ELM">
                    <documentation>ELM,
              A segment providing details of any variation or restriction
              of the current data element as used in this context.
              Typically this segment will convey details of restricted size
              or character representation.</documentation>
                </segment>
                <segment ignoreUnmappedFields="false" maxOccurs="1" minOccurs="0" name="Editing details" nodeTypeRef="UN:EDT" segcode="EDT" truncatable="true" xmltag="EDT">
                    <documentation>EDT,
              A segment providing details of any editing information such
              as maximum field length and status that would be used by a
              screen-based editor, forms input or data output process when
              physical representation of the data carried in a data message
              using this implementation guide is required.</documentation>
                </segment>
                <segment ignoreUnmappedFields="false" maxOccurs="9" minOccurs="0" name="Item description" nodeTypeRef="UN:IMD" segcode="IMD" truncatable="true" xmltag="IMD">
                    <documentation>IMD,
              A segment providing further details of presentational
              information such as text alignment and style that might be
              used by a screen-based editor, forms input or data output
              process when physical representation of the data carried in a
              data message using this implementation guide is required.</documentation>
                </segment>
                <segment ignoreUnmappedFields="false" maxOccurs="9" minOccurs="0" name="Processing information" nodeTypeRef="UN:GEI" segcode="GEI" truncatable="true" xmltag="GEI">
                    <documentation>GEI,
              A segment providing further details of processing information
              such as data handling, positioning or control that might be
              used by a screen-based editor, forms input or data output
              process when data is carried, stored or collected by a data
              message using this implementation guide is required.</documentation>
                </segment>
                <segment ignoreUnmappedFields="false" maxOccurs="99" minOccurs="0" name="Free text" nodeTypeRef="UN:FTX" segcode="FTX" truncatable="true" xmltag="FTX">
                    <documentation>FTX,
              A segment providing implementation guide notes, or other
              textual information relating to this element usage. The
              segment will also be used to carry the final set of
              information that would be used by a screen-based editor;
              forms input or data output process; a legend or user-
              recognisable description; and a help text.</documentation>
                </segment>
            </segmentGroup>
            <segmentGroup maxOccurs="999" minOccurs="0" xmltag="Segment_group_9">
                <documentation>Segment group 9:
           A group of segments specifying implementation requirements for
           the number of instances of repeating segments, segment groups or
           elements in the current context. Multiple instances of this
           segment group will typically be used to describe both the
           overall limits of usage and to identify individual instances in
           any given context.</documentation>
                <segment ignoreUnmappedFields="false" maxOccurs="1" minOccurs="1" name="Measurements" nodeTypeRef="UN:MEA" segcode="MEA" truncatable="true" xmltag="MEA">
                    <documentation>MEA,
              A segment to measure the number of instances of usage of a
              component in a message. The segment may specify minima,
              maxima, range or instance criteria.</documentation>
                </segment>
                <segment ignoreUnmappedFields="false" maxOccurs="99" minOccurs="0" name="Free text" nodeTypeRef="UN:FTX" segcode="FTX" truncatable="true" xmltag="FTX">
                    <documentation>FTX,
              A segment providing implementation guide notes, or other
              textual information relating to this measurement.</documentation>
                </segment>
            </segmentGroup>
            <segmentGroup maxOccurs="99999" minOccurs="0" xmltag="Segment_group_10">
                <documentation>Segment group 10:
           A group of segments specifying the usage of values for a non-
           coded data element. Multiple instances of this segment group may
           be used to provide a complete set of ranges or specific values,
           including preferences. It can be used for any other type of data
           element, such as strings, numerics, dates and times. It can also
           specify a default value and associated implementation notes for
           a specific element in a particular context. 
           
           A simple element or component element context must have been
           established before this segment group is used.</documentation>
                <segment ignoreUnmappedFields="false" maxOccurs="1" minOccurs="1" name="Element value definition" nodeTypeRef="UN:ELV" segcode="ELV" truncatable="true" xmltag="ELV">
                    <documentation>ELV,
              A segment identifying one or more components of an element
              value constraint series. It also may provide a default value
              for the current element context. This is expressed in a
              single text field so as to be used by or applicable to the
              broadest range of applications.</documentation>
                </segment>
                <segment ignoreUnmappedFields="false" maxOccurs="99" minOccurs="0" name="Free text" nodeTypeRef="UN:FTX" segcode="FTX" truncatable="true" xmltag="FTX">
                    <documentation>FTX,
              A segment providing implementation guide notes, or other
              textual information related to the particular context. Such a
              context may include implementation guide notes for the
              default value.</documentation>
                </segment>
            </segmentGroup>
            <segmentGroup maxOccurs="99999" minOccurs="0" xmltag="Segment_group_11">
                <documentation>Segment group 11:
           A group of segments specifying the usage of code values for a
           coded data element. Multiple instances of this segment group may
           be used to provide a complete set of code values, including
           preferences.
           
           A simple element or component element context must have been
           established before this segment group is used.</documentation>
                <segment ignoreUnmappedFields="false" maxOccurs="1" minOccurs="1" name="Code value definition" nodeTypeRef="UN:CDV" segcode="CDV" truncatable="true" xmltag="CDV">
                    <documentation>CDV,
              A segment identifying the code value, its source and usage
              preference.</documentation>
                </segment>
                <segment ignoreUnmappedFields="false" maxOccurs="99" minOccurs="0" name="Free text" nodeTypeRef="UN:FTX" segcode="FTX" truncatable="true" xmltag="FTX">
                    <documentation>FTX,
              A segment providing implementation guide notes, or other
              textual information related to the particular context.</documentation>
                </segment>
            </segmentGroup>
            <segmentGroup maxOccurs="99999" minOccurs="0" xmltag="Segment_group_12">
                <documentation>Segment group 12:
           A group of segments specifying data representation details for a
           component of the message. This segment group may be used in a
           segment, group, composite or simple data element context to
           describe the data representation that the implementation guide
           author intends to use to hold, store or represent the structure
           or data in a non-EDI environment.</documentation>
                <segment ignoreUnmappedFields="false" maxOccurs="1" minOccurs="1" name="Data representation details" nodeTypeRef="UN:DRD" segcode="DRD" truncatable="true" xmltag="DRD">
                    <documentation>DRD,
              A segment identifying an underlying data representation by
              tag, basic data type and size. This is the representation
              itself, and not a pointer to an external document.</documentation>
                </segment>
                <segment ignoreUnmappedFields="false" maxOccurs="99" minOccurs="0" name="Free text" nodeTypeRef="UN:FTX" segcode="FTX" truncatable="true" xmltag="FTX">
                    <documentation>FTX,
              A segment providing implementation guide notes, or other
              relevant textual information.</documentation>
                </segment>
            </segmentGroup>
        </segmentGroup>
        <segmentGroup maxOccurs="1" minOccurs="0" xmltag="Segment_group_13">
            <documentation>Segment group 13:
        A group of segments to provide authentication for the message.</documentation>
            <segment ignoreUnmappedFields="false" maxOccurs="1" minOccurs="1" name="Authentication result" nodeTypeRef="UN:AUT" segcode="AUT" truncatable="true" xmltag="AUT">
                <documentation>AUT,
           A segment specifying the details of any authentication
           (validation) procedure applied to the IMPDEF message.</documentation>
            </segment>
            <segment ignoreUnmappedFields="false" maxOccurs="1" minOccurs="0" name="Date/time/period" nodeTypeRef="UN:DTM" segcode="DTM" truncatable="true" xmltag="DTM">
                <documentation>DTM,
           A segment specifying the date of authentication.</documentation>
            </segment>
        </segmentGroup>
    </segments>
</edimap>
